<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tasks on Programming thoughts</title>
    <link>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/tasks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tasks on Programming thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://trinhduyhung.github.io/tasks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/tasks/best-practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/tasks/best-practices/</guid>
      <description>Best practice
 (My rule) Implement things following open source standard: for example how to implement a log client PECS - &amp;ldquo;Producer - Extends, Consumer - Super&amp;rdquo;: The Get and Put Principle: use an extends wildcard when you only get values our of a structure, use a super wildcard when you only put values into a structure, and don&amp;rsquo;t use a wildcard you both get and put. (Java) Generally, it&amp;rsquo;s not a good practice to modify variables used in lambda expressions and anonymous classes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/tasks/post-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/tasks/post-progress/</guid>
      <description>Posts in progress Linux introduction:  Ken Thompson: developed UNIX at Bell Labs Linux for newbies: advantages, why and how to study, installation, alternatives The PDP-7 was used by Thompson for first version of UNIX Linux definition by The Linux Information Project (LINFO) Famous quotations about Linux, by The Linux Information Project (LINFO) What is Linux? An in-depth introduction Intro To Linux [For Beginners] - DEV  Linux shell  Shell definition by The Linux Information Project (LINFO) How to change Shells by The Linux Information Project (LINFO)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/tasks/spring-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/tasks/spring-notes/</guid>
      <description>@SpringBootApplication is a convenience annotation that adds all of the following:
  @Configuration: Tags the class as a source of bean definitions for the application context.
  @EnableAutoConfiguration: Tells Spring Boot to start adding beans based on classpath settings, other beans, and various property settings. For example, if spring-webmvc is on the classpath, this annotation flags the application as a web application and activates key behaviors, such as setting up a DispatcherServlet.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>