<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Programming thoughts</title>
    <link>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Programming thoughts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 11:51:24 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://trinhduyhung.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Widening and narrowing in Java</title>
      <link>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/posts/widening-narrowing-in-java/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 11:51:24 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/posts/widening-narrowing-in-java/</guid>
      <description>While reading the Java language specification (JLS 14), I immediately pay attention to the chapter 5 where it describes how widening and narrowing for primitive data types works in Java. It&amp;rsquo;s because I&amp;rsquo;m always interested in somethings that go behind the sense, somethings that are at a low level, for example things related to binary representation of data.
Java has the following primitive data types that are summarized in a table like so:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Linux</title>
      <link>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/posts/introduction-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2020 16:27:26 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/posts/introduction-linux/</guid>
      <description>A brief history of Unix It all started in 1969 when Ken Thompson wrote his game named Space Travel that simulates travel in the Solar System. He originally wrote it for use on Multics (Multiplexed Information and Computing Service) operating system, but soon after Bell Labs pulled out of the Multics project, he rewrote it for the obsolete and little-used PDP-7 minicomputer that he found at his neighboring department. While writing this game on the PDP-7, he decided to implement his own base code libraries for the game to use including arithmetic, packages and graphics subsystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure multiple Github accounts on a single machine</title>
      <link>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/posts/multiple-github-accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 11:06:25 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://trinhduyhung.github.io/posts/multiple-github-accounts/</guid>
      <description>Sooner or later as a developer, you will find yourself in a situation where you’re working using multiple Github accounts. One is your company account, one is your personal account. In this post, I’m going to share a common approach that can help you achieve that.
We will be using ssh as the protocol to authenticate our git requests to Github server because we do not want to enter the password each time we do a git request using username/password authentication.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>